{
    "subject": "Cliff_Robertson",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Dina_Merrill",
    "human_readable": "Cliff Robertson is married to Dina Merrill.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885679483413696,
            "question": "Is Dina Merrill married to Cliff Robertson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9839913845062256,
            "question": "Have Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill been married for a long time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9807741045951843,
            "question": "Are Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill still married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9770382642745972,
            "question": "When did Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill get married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9536513090133667,
            "question": "Are there any public records about Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill's marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9279184937477112,
            "question": "Who is Cliff Robertson married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8731974363327026,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7217884063720703,
            "question": "What is the name of Cliff Robertson's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7070518136024475,
            "question": "Do Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill have children together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5842224359512329,
            "question": "Who is Dina Merrill?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cliff Robertson is married to Dina Merrill.",
            "html": "yago_22806_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill have children together?",
            "html": "yago_22806_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Cliff Robertson's wife?",
            "html": "yago_22806_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the relationship between Cliff Robertson and Dina Merrill?",
            "html": "yago_22806_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22806_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The first document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22806/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt) mentions Dina Merrill and Cliff Robertson were married for 21 years.\n* The second document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22806/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt) confirms that they were married, mentioning their marriage as one of her notable relationships.\n* The third document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22806/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt) shows a photo of them smiling together after their wedding.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Dina Merrill and Cliff Robertson, indicating that they were indeed married. Therefore, the triple \"Cliff Robertson is married to Dina Merrill\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}